Contact

glawry45@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gaynellelawry-msn-rn-cmsrn-153926100 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Healthcare Management

Languages

English

Certifications

CMSRN

Gaynelle Lawry MSN, RN, CMSRN

Clinical Manager II at Memorial Hermann Health System Cypress, Texas

Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing, Inpatient Care, Hospitals, Healthcare, and Healthcare Management. Strong professional with a Master of Science (MSN) focused in Nursing Education from William Carey College.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System Clinical Nurse Manager II August 2007 - Present (12 years 10 months)

Lone Star College Previous Adjunct Professor of Nursing June 2010 - June 2011 (1 year 1 month) Kingwood, Texas

Education

William Carey College
Master of Science (MSN), Nursing Education · (2009 - 2010)

William Carey University College
Bachelor of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1996 - 2000)